<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="POETS">
        <item>William Wordsworth</item>
        <item>Edgar Allan Poe</item>
        <item>Alexander Pushkin</item>
        <item>William Blake</item>
        <item>Rudyard Kipling</item>
        <item>Samuel Taylor Coleridge</item>
        <item>Rabindranath Tagore</item>
        <item>Elizabeth Barrett Browning</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="ICONS">
        <item>@drawable/img_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_6</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_7</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_8</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="POEMS">
        <item>" I wandered lonely as a cloud \n"
            "That floats on high o'er vales and hills,\n"
            "When all at once I saw a crowd,\n"
            "A host, of golden daffodils;\n"
            "Beside the lake, beneath the trees,\n"
            "Fluttering and dancing in the breeze.\n"
            "Continuous as the stars that shine\n"
            "And twinkle on the milky way,\n"
            "They stretched in never-ending line\n"
            "Along the margin of a bay:\n"
            "Ten thousand saw I at a glance,\n"
            "Tossing their heads in sprightly dance."</item>

        <item>" Take this kiss upon the brow!\n"
            "And, in parting from you now,\n"
            "Thus much let me avow\n"
            "You are not wrong, who deem\n"
            "That my days have been a dream;\n"
            "Yet if hope has flown away\n"
            "In a night, or in a day,\n"
            "In a vision, or in none,\n"
            "Is it therefore the less gone?\n"
            "All that we see or seem\n"
            "Is but a dream within a dream."</item>

        <item>" I loved you, and I probably still do,\n"
            "And for a while the feeling may remain\n"
            "But let my love no longer trouble you,\n"
            "I do not wish to cause you any pain.\n"
            "I loved you;\n"
            "and the hopelessness I knew,\n"
            "The jealousy, the shyness\n"
            "- though in vain -\n"
            "Made up a love so tender and so true\n"
            "As may God grant you to be loved again."</item>

        <item>" Tyger! Tyger! burning bright\n"
            "In the forest of the night\n"
            "What immortal hand or eye\n"
            "Could frame thy fearful symmetry?\n"
            "In what distant deeps or skies\n"
            "Burnt the fire of thine eyes?\n"
            "On what wings dare he aspire?\n"
            "What the hand dare seize the fire?\n"
            "And what shoulder, and what art,\n"
            "Could twist the sinews of thy heart?\n"
            "And when thy heart began to beat,\n"
            "What dread hand? and what dread feet?."</item>

        <item>" If you can talk with crowds and keep your virtue,\n"
            "Or walk with Kings — nor lose the common touch,\n"
            "If neither foes nor loving friends can hurt you,\n"
            "If all men count with you, but none too much;\n"
            "If you can fill the unforgiving minute\n"
            "With sixty seconds’ worth of distance run,\n"
            "Yours is the Earth and everything that’s in it,\n"
            "And — which is more — you’ll be a Man, my son!"</item>

        <item>" In Xanadu did Kubla Khan\n"
            "A stately pleasure-dome decree:\n"
            "Where Alph, the sacred river, ran\n"
            "Through caverns measureless to man\n"
            "Down to a sunless sea.\n"
            "So twice five miles of fertile ground\n"
            "With walls and towers were girdled round:\n"
            "And there were gardens bright with sinuous rills,\n"
            "Where blossomed many an incense-bearing tree;\n"
            "And here were forests ancient as the hills,\n"
            "Enfolding sunny spots of greenery."</item>

        <item>" Where the mind is without fear and the head is held high;\n"
            "Where knowledge is free;\n"
            "Where the world has not been broken up\n "
            "into fragments by narrow domestic walls;\n"
            "Where words come out from the depth of truth;\n"
            "Where tireless striving stretches its arms towards perfection:\n"
            "Where the clear stream of reason has not lost its way\n "
            "into the dreary desert sand of dead habit;\n"
            "Where the mind is lead forward by thee\n"
            "Into ever-widening thought and action–\n"
            "Into that heaven of freedom, my Father, let my country awake."</item>

        <item>" How do I love thee? Let me count the ways.\n"
            "I love thee to the depth and breadth and height\n"
            "My soul can reach, when feeling out of sight\n"
            "For the ends of Being and ideal Grace.\n"
            "I love thee to the level of every day’s\n"
            "Most quiet need, by sun and candlelight.\n"
            "I love thee freely, as men strive for Right;\n"
            "I love thee purely, as they turn from Praise.\n"
            "I love with a passion put to use\n"
            "In my old griefs, and with my childhood’s faith."</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>